the [ __ ] tweets that I wrote something I
los [__] tweets que yo escribía algo te
passed it to you and you know it and there's
lo pasaba a ti y tú lo sabes y hay
evidence within the group and I'm going to
pruebas dentro del grupo y las voy a
look for it I put a screenshot and you say
buscar te pongo una captura y tú dices
that like that no that's Food that remove it that's
eso así no eso es Food eso quítalo eso
out you have to put it in such another
fuera tienes que ponerlo de tal otra
way
manera
literally also many tws were
literal también muchos tws eran
exactly There we are and that It was you
exactamente Ahí estamos y eso Fuiste tú
instead of recognizing your involvement in this
en lugar de reconocer tu implicación al
regard what you did was
respecto de eso lo que hiciste fue
start lying about it pretending
ponerte a mentir al respecto fingiendo
that you had nothing to
que tú no tenías nada que
do you just acknowledged the
hac acaba ra de reconocer lo de los
tweets or was it a smoke of mine Yeah yeah you just
tweet o ha sido una fumada mía Sí sí lo
acknowledged it [ __ ] Ah I didn't
acaba de reconocer [__] Ah que yo no
know a [ __ ] thing in [ __ ] If
sabía una [__] [__] en crip Si
you knew you told me to post those [ __ ]
supieras me dicho poner esos [__]
tweets send your people to sell it wasn't
tweets mandar a tu gente a vender no fue
the mistake the mistake was the tweets I
el error el error fueron los tweets Te
introduce you to Diana and then you were
presento a Diana y después estabas de
partying with her because I went partying
fiesta con ella porque me fui de fiesta
with Diana are you angry Who is Diana
con Diana estás enfadado Quién es diana
dasas
dasas